A Finding Aid to the Wilna Hervey and Nan Mason Papers, 1883-1985, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Personal Files of Dan Mason, 1919-1928; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 0.4 Linear feet Box 12
  - Correspondence from Nan Mason, 1927 February-1928; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence from Wilna Hervey, 1926-1927; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1922-1927; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Envelopes, 1924-1928; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Memoirs, circa 1920s; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 12, Folder 13-15)
  - Financial Records, 1919-1927; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Clippings, circa 1924-1926; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 17)